Why do I got to choose between working out versus having a good hair week?
You don't have to choose.
You just have to change your mindset and fully realize that you can take your hair with you anywhere,
particularly in the shower.
You can.
Your hair loves everywhere you go.
So the problem has been that you've kept your hair away from going into the places that you would go
and you wouldn't take her with you.
But she loves water and conditioner.
She loves it.
You know, if you understand how to take care of your natural texture,
you can be the switch it up girl and wear it however you choose.
But it's important to realize that your hair wants to go in the shower with you.
It wants to go, baby.
Take it.
It does.
White people take a wash rag in the shower with you.
It wants to go with you.
Right.
But you won't take your hair in the shower with you and you'll talk about her.
Yeah.
That's it.
Okay.
I'll get you.
Yeah.
Alright.
Bye.